### About me

I'm ZCPE (Zend Certified PHP Engineer) and I work with PHP since 2009, passionate for open-source, patterns, tests and source code well written. Always looking for best practices, new technologies and methodologies to improve my workflow and bring great results to the project and to my customer.

### Skills

Languages, Tools and Technologies				Certifications
■ PHP	<ul><li>Wordpress</li></ul>	■ Grunt	<ul><li>Javascript</li></ul>	<ul><li>Zend Certified</li></ul>
MVC/MVVM	PHPUnit	■ Git	■ jQuery	PHP Engineer
Zend	<ul><li>Doctrine</li></ul>	<ul><li>SVN</li></ul>	<ul><li>Angular</li></ul>	
<ul><li>Symfony</li></ul>	<ul><li>Vagrant</li></ul>	Windows	HTML/CSS/Less	5
<ul><li>Silex</li></ul>	<ul><li>Apache</li></ul>	■ Linux	<ul><li>TwitterBootstra</li></ul>	ар
<ul><li>Laravel</li></ul>	<ul><li>MySQL</li></ul>	<ul><li>OSX</li></ul>	■ Java	

# Experience

FlixBus GmbH PHP Engineer Currently

 Changing the life of approximately one billion of people commute, spending their weekends, building remote relationships, visiting relatives, and discovering the world.

NeoGrid Senior PHP Developer 2015 - 2017

- Created a web application using Material Design and AngularJS to the front-end and Silex to the back-end that automated the sales of the WebEDI solution;
- Implemented improvements, bug fixes and integrations with NeoGrid solutions using REST APIs;
- Added the Vagrant tool to use with my team in order to use environments identical with the production environment;
- Evangelist of best practices of programming following the existent PSRs and implementing unit test in the projects;
- Reference in my team to projects that was written in PHP and AngularJS;
- Recently I'm working on a Java project that will create a new solution to be sold by NeoGrid.

Humantech PHP Developer 2015 - 2015

- Lead the team (five workers) as assistant manager of the programming department when the manager was not present;
- Added unit tests in critical project parts, reducing considerable the amount of bugs and increasing the quality of projects;
- Created an e-learning platform using the gamification concepts.

A2C PHP Developer 2013 - 2014

- Created a CMS to the 3M brand using the gamification concepts and fully focused on SEO, that resulted in three times more access to the website in few months;
- Created a software to monitor the reputation of political candidates in social networks, that give more visibility on medias to the agency;
- Reference in my team to projects that was written in Symfony 2;
- Responsible to manage the Amazon Web Services EC2, RDS and S3.

# Education

## **UNISOCIESC**

## **BSc Information Systems**

2011 - 2014

- Honor as the best student of the course;
- The final paper is based on a tool created to be used by professionals that are studying to achieve the ZCPE certification, the project is open-source and is available on GitHub, the project is hosted by "DigitalOcean" as a sponsor.

## Courses

English Live Going to the fluency Currently

• I'm having classes with a private teacher about a lot of topics to be fluent discussing anything.